[
    {
      "question":
        "BST search, insert, and delete operations typically run in time O(d). What is d?",
      "answers": [
        "The number of divisions at each level",  
        "The total number of entries in all the nodes of the tree",
        "The depth of the relevant node in the tree",
        "The number of entries in each node",
        "The number of nodes in the tree"
      ],
      "correct": "The depth of the relevant node in the tree",
      "checkedOption":"",
      "questionId": "000001"
    },
    {
      "question":
      "A binary tree is another name for a BST.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "False",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000002"
    },
    {
      "question":
      "RAM access time is normally measured in:",
    "answers": [
      "Nanoseconds (billionths of a second)", 
      "Milliseconds (thousandths of a second)",
      "Microseconds (millionths of a second)"
    ],
    "correct": "Nanoseconds (billionths of a second)",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000003"
    },
    {
      "question":
      "The Sequential Search algorithm is in O(n^2)O(n2).",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "True",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000004"
    },
    {
      "question":
      "Given an array-based list implementation, deleting the current element takes how long in the average case?",
    "answers": ["Θ(nlogn) time", "Θ(n) time", "Θ(1) time","Θ(logn) time"],
    "correct": "Θ(n) time",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000005"
    },
    {
      "question":
      "An advantage of linked lists over the array-based list implementation is:",
    "answers": [
       "Expandability",
       "Low access cost to arbitrary positions",
       "None of these","Θ(logn) time", 
       "Zero overhead",
       "Optimal search speed"],
    "correct": "Expandability",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000006"
    },{
      "question":
      "Which of these is the best upper bound for a growth rate of 5n + 3?",
    "answers": [
       "O(1)",
       "O(logn)",
       "O(nlogn)", 
       "O(n)"],
    "correct": "O(n)",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000007"
    },{
      "question":
      "Determine the proper relationship between the pair of functions: f(n)=10 and g(n)=log 10 ",
    "answers": [
      "f(n)is in Ω(g(n))", 
      "f(n)is Θ(g(n))",
      "f(n) is in O(g(n))"
    ],
    "correct": "f(n)is Θ(g(n))",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000008"
    },{
      "question":
      "The worst case upper bound for sorting an array is O(nlogn) since this is the cost of the best algorithm (in the worst case) that we know about.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "True",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000009"
    },{
      "question":
      "An inversion is:",
    "answers": [
      "A swap",
      "When a record with key value greater than the current record's key appears before it in the array",
      "A type of sort"
    ],
    "correct": "When a record with key value greater than the current record's key appears before it in the array",
    "checkedOption":"",
    "questionId": "000010"
    }
  
  ]